Lais Zagati

Email | GitHub | LinkedIn

+353 89 214 9883

PERSONAL PROFILE

Entry-level full stack web developer, currently enrolled in a Diploma in Full stack software development with code Institute. Experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python. Have had exposure to project management, object-oriented programming, and testing. I have professional experience of over 8 years in customer experience in different industries. I bring an excellent customer service background plus technical abilities that proves my strong interpersonal skills and that I am logical, responsive, ambitious and resourceful.

EDUCATION

2024 - Currently: Code Institute - Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

2024 - Currently: Zero To Mastery Academy (Udemy) - Complete Python Development

2023 - Currently: Zero To Mastery Academy (Udemy) - Complete Web Developer

TECHNICAL SKILL SET

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Python

Project Management: Trello board, lucid chart, Gannt chart, Agile

Modules: Programming and implementation, object-oriented programming, software testing

Additional IT Skills: Microsoft Azure, Microsoft Office, Google Meet, Slack

Version Control: Git, GitHub

PERSONAL SKILL SET

Strong communication skills

Proactive problem solver

Team player

• Customer Relationship Management

- Proactive problem solver
- Analytical mindset
- Results focused
- Strong leadership skills

COLLABORATIVE PROJECT

Had the initiative to develop the Airline Billing Calculator for my team, witnessing the time-saving benefits it brought to my team at Cencora was gratifying. Creating the airline charges calculator showcased my ability to streamline processes and improve efficiency through automation. This project, developed using HTML, JavaScript, and CSS, exemplifies my technical skills and problem-solving capabilities. I am eager to leverage these experiences to contribute effectively to future projects and initiatives, driving innovation and excellence in the IT industry.

INTERESTS/ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Participation in Tech Meetups (e.g. Empowering Women in Tech, React & MongoDB Dublin Meetup).
- I attend regular networking events (e.g. Women in Technology Networking, Women in Tech Dublin, GDG Dublin Events, Pycon2024).
 - I spend plenty of time watching YouTube tutorials on programming and taking additional certifications.
 - I enjoy doing coding challenges online.
 - Learning and gaining useful skills through reading, courses and networking meet-ups.
 - I am a challenge-seeker and that is what dragged me to the Tech world.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cencora, Inc. | Logistics Coordinator | [Full-Time]

Jan 2024 - Currently | Dublin, Ireland

- Support the planning and execution of shipment orders from initial order placement to the physical preparation of shipments prior to dispatch to the airport, all while providing the highest level of customer service offerings and operational capabilities.
- Undertake various administrative tasks to ensure everything runs in a seamless manner.
- Communicate effectively with associates, transporters, and airlines to optimize services.

Colorman Ireland | Customer Service & Fulfilment Coordinator | [Full-Time]

May 2021 - Jan 2024 | Dublin, Ireland

- Managed the order fulfilment process specifically for customers of Oracle's products and services by ensuring that customer orders were processed accurately and efficiently.
- Was solely responsible for the quality inbound checks, ensuring the accuracy and quality of incoming products or materials.

Your Dream Intercambio | Customer Care Specialist & Business Development | [Full-Time]

Jan 2016 – April 2021 | Dublin, Ireland

- Developed a strong background in business development and customer success by researching and targeting new clients, creating effective messaging, and collaborating with teams to meet customer needs.
- Led a diverse team, built partnerships, coordinated with clients, and actively pursued new business opportunities through market research.

OTHER EDUCATION & INFORMATION

Portuguese Native Speaker.

2020 - 2021 - QQI Level 5 Applied Psychology course - BFEI (Ireland).

2012- 2015 - Tourism and Business Management - FMU (Brazil)